<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RCF TTC</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">drawer open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">drawer close</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_events">Events</string>
    <string name="title_activity_event">Event</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_event_saini">Events</string>
    <string name="show_more"><![CDATA[Swipe up for more]]></string>
    <string name="third">  “Kaivalya 2K18” is scheduled to be organized on 18th and 19th of April 2018. For the convenience of anyone in the world to participate, we have made the major events of Kaivalya including the signature event “Gambit” online, but we would recommend everyone to visit the beautiful place and also give us a chance of hospitality. The minor events will however be conducted only onsite. With exciting prizes and no participation fees, and the convenience of participating just with an internet connection from anywhere in the world, you have nothing to lose. So, find the event that suits you the most, enrol yourself and gear up, because the challenges are only going to get better and harder.</string>
    <string name="sec"> Technical Training Centre was established in the year 1987 with a purpose to enhance the potential of the newly recruited employees and to meet the immediate training need.Now a days, Technical Training Centre is not only imparting training to RCF employees but also sharing the responsibility of "Product based training" to all zonal railways and production units as per their requirements. Technical Training Centre is established within RCF campus itself in its natural, lush green and peaceful environment.</string>

    <string name="at_kav_droid_we_give_developers_from_colleges_a_chance_to_create_an_android_application_and_win_exciting_prizes_kaiv_droid_is_a_team_event_with_a_team_of_up_to_3_members_this_event_is_to_be_hosted_online_on_hackerearth_com_kaiv_droid_will_be_in_two_rounds_preliminary_qualification_round_and_a_main_round_for_preliminary_round_a_task_will_be_provided_at_hackerearth_com_1_week_prior_to_the_main_kaivalya_event_the_time_to_complete_the_task_will_be_5_days_and_after_5_days_submissions_will_be_checked_and_teams_will_be_selected_for_main_round_based_on_the_performance_the_main_round_will_proceed_during_the_kaivalya_event_and_in_main_round_one_functionality_will_be_required_to_be_added_in_the_previously_submitted_application_the_task_will_go_live_during_the_start_of_the_event_and_the_time_for_task_completion_is_3_hours_the_final_result_will_be_calculated_on_the_basis_of_performance_in_both_pre_and_main_round_more_than_an_event_kav_droid_is_a_platform_to_make_you_reach_to_the_common_man_with_your_development_skills_and_creativity_so_don_t_wait_for_registering_yourself">At “Kav-Droid”, we give developers from colleges a chance to create an Android Application and win exciting prizes. Kaiv- Droid is a team event with a team of up to 3 members. This event is to be hosted online on hackerearth.com. Kaiv-Droid will be in two rounds (preliminary qualification round and a main round). For preliminary round a task will be provided at hackerearth.com 1 week prior to the main Kaivalya event. The time to complete the task will be 5 days and after 5 days submissions will be checked and teams will be selected for main round based on the performance. The main round will proceed during the Kaivalya event and in main round, one functionality will be required to be added in the previously submitted application. The task will go live during the start of the event and the time for task completion is 3 hours. The final result will be calculated on the basis of performance in both pre and main round. More than an event, “Kav-Droid” is a platform to make you reach to the common man with your development skills and creativity, so don’t wait for registering yourself.</string>
    <string name="gambit_is_the_signature_event_of_kaivalya_the_annual_activity_fest_of_the_computer_science_department_btkit_dwarahat_it_is_an_online_situation_coding_competition_conducted_on_codechef_com_that_allows_participants_college_students_to_appear_online_from_anywhere_in_the_world_the_duration_of_gambit_2018_is_5_hours_and_30_minutes_and_it_will_start_at_post_lunch_time_2_p_m_ist_or_later_and_be_over_by_evening_participants_from_colleges_are_also_encouraged_to_participate_onsite_at_btkit_campus_proper_internet_facility_and_refreshments_will_be_provided_there_will_be_10_challenges_to_be_solved_in_minimum_amount_of_time_and_winners_will_be_decided_based_on_factors_like_number_of_problems_solved_time_taken_and_accuracy_of_solutions">Gambit is the signature event of “Kaivalya”, the annual Activity Fest of the Computer Science Department, BTKIT Dwarahat. It is an online situation coding competition conducted on codechef.com that allows participants (College Students) to appear online from anywhere in the world. The duration of Gambit 2018 is 5 Hours and 30 Minutes and it will start at post lunch time (2 P.M. IST or later) and be over by evening. Participants from colleges are also encouraged to participate onsite at BTKIT campus. Proper Internet facility and refreshments will be provided. There will be 10 challenges to be solved in minimum amount of time and winners will be decided based on factors like number of problems solved, time taken and accuracy of solutions.</string>
    <string name="webmaster_is_a_team_event_which_is_conducted_both_online_on_hackerearth_com_and_onsite_in_btkit_campus_with_preliminary_and_main_round_preliminary_round_or_qualification_round_is_the_core_of_the_competition_in_which_we_give_you_the_theme_and_you_give_us_the_design_complete_web_application_needs_to_be_submitted_with_all_functionality_and_innovation_selected_teams_will_qualify_for_the_main_round_in_which_a_specific_functionality_needs_to_be_added_on_the_web_application_to_test_on_the_spot_skills_of_the_team_the_task_for_the_main_round_will_go_live_during_the_commencement_of_the_main_round_and_the_duration_will_be_3_hours_at_the_end_of_the_round_final_submissions_will_be_made_and_winner_will_be_decided_on_the_basis_of_overall_score_of_preliminary_and_main_round">Webmaster is a team event which is conducted both online on hackerearth.com and onsite in BTKIT Campus with preliminary and main round. Preliminary round or qualification round is the core of the competition in which we give you the theme and you give us the design. Complete web application needs to be submitted with all functionality and innovation. Selected teams will qualify for the main round in which a specific functionality needs to be added on the web application to test “On the Spot” skills of the team. The task for the main round will go live during the commencement of the main round. And the duration will be 3 hours. At the end of the round, final submissions will be made and winner will be decided on the basis of overall score of preliminary and main round.</string>
    <string name="at_ideathon_idea_is_yours_and_platform_is_ours_this_year_in_presentech_we_have_not_put_any_barrier_on_the_field_of_your_idea_if_you_have_an_idea_be_it_a_business_one_or_a_technological_one_register_with_presentech_and_present_it_to_us_presentech_is_an_onsite_event_to_be_conducted_in_btkit_campus_in_this_event_you_have_to_give_us_a_presentation_on_your_idea_and_explain_to_us_about_it_this_is_an_individual_event_and_person_with_the_best_idea_will_be_deemed_as_the_winner">At “Ideathon”, idea is yours and platform is ours. This year in Presentech, we have not put any barrier on the field of your idea. If you have an idea, be it a business one or a technological one, register with Presentech and present it to us. Presentech is an onsite event to be conducted in BTKIT Campus. In this event you have to give us a presentation on your idea and explain to us about it. This is an individual event and person with the best idea will be deemed as the winner.</string>
    <string name="iron">In “Iron Out”, you get tangled or buggy code and you have to extract functioning code or a piece of information out of it. Iron Out is organised in one round only and is an onsite team event with a team of up to 3 members. The duration of the event is 1 hour and there are few pieces of tangled code which you have to sort out. Each problem has marks assigned to it and the team with maximum score will be deemed as the winner.</string>
    <string name="rit">In “R U Ritchie”, you get multiple choice questions on C and you have to answer them correctly and accurately. This is an onsite only event organised in BTKIT Campus. This is an individual event and the participant with maximum of the score will be deemed the winner. Each wrong answer can also cost you a penalty, so better be accurate.</string>
    <string name="tet">Geographically, we are located amidst the hills of North India. To some, we might merely be a valley in Himalayas but we speak Technology. We are the Computing Club of BTKIT Dwarahat, Uttarakhand and we proudly present Kaivalya 2K18, one of its own kind in India. Bipin Tripathi, Kumaun Institute of Technology, Dwarahat is a Technical Institute of Uttarakhand Government that is situated near the hills of District Almora.</string>
    <string name="an">Regional Welding Training Institute was Established in Dec. 2002 in Rail Factory with a view to enhance welding skills of Supervisors and Technicians RCE DMW, Northern Railway and North Western Railway.
RWTI has well equipped, modernized welding shop and test lab and peaceful environment for learning, environment friendly class rooms.

WELDING SHOP

Welding shop has latest infrastructure having sufficient number of MMAW and MIG/MAG, Digital-Pulse type MIG/MAG, Inverter Based TIG Welding. Submerged Arc Welding with Gouging Facility, Spot Welding machine.
Besides above, Welding Fume Extraction System has been provided to take care of the health of Trainees.

WELD TEST LAB

RWTI has a new weld test lab to enhance the awareness about welding quality by various testing methods.
Lab is equipped with Universal Testing Machine, Rockwell Hardness Testing Machine, Impact Testing Machine, Heating Furnace, Magna-flux Testing Machine, Inverted Metallurgical Microscope and Micro-polisher.</string>
    <string name="ritt">For all of us, Computer Geeks, “C” is the mother tongue. C, being the legendary programming language can well be described as the hardest to learn as well. This event challenges you to prove your mastery over C. In “R U Ritchie”, you get multiple choice questions on C and you have to answer them correctly and accurately. This is an onsite only event organised in BTKIT Campus. This is an individual event and the participant with maximum of the score will be deemed the winner. Each wrong answer can also cost you a penalty, so better be accurate. C, although taught in the most basic of the programming courses, yet believed to be hardest of the languages to learn, is itself an art. And if you have that art, then exhibit us in “R U Ritchie”, which by no means is an easy challenge.</string>
    <string name="cicada">Cicada 3301 logo Cicada 3301 is a nickname given to an organization that on six occasions has posted a set of puzzles and alternate reality games to possibly recruit codebreakers/linguists from the public.Cicada 3301 logo
Cicada 3301 is a nickname given to an organization that on six occasions has posted a set of puzzles and alternate reality games to possibly recruit codebreakers/linguists from the public.[1] The first internet puzzle started on January 4, 2012, and ran for approximately one month. A second round began one year later on January 4, 2013, and a third round following the confirmation of a fresh clue posted on Twitter on January 4, 2014.[2][3] The stated intent was to recruit "intelligent individuals" by presenting a series of puzzles which were to be solved. No new puzzles were published on January 4, 2015. However, a new clue was posted on Twitter on January 5, 2016.[4][5] In April 2017 another PGP-signed message was found: Beware false paths. Always verify PGP signature from 7A35090F.[6] That message explicitly denies the validity of any unsigned puzzle, as recently as April 2017.

.</string>
    <string name="webd">A workshop on "Web Designing and Development" organized by BTKIT coding club. A career in Web designing can prove every bit as rewarding and much more fun! Also it improves your job prospects and get an edge over your counterparts.
This is a  workshop on HTML and Open Source Technologies PHP and MYSQL. Learn web designing from basic HTML to advance HTML and add functionality to websites using JavaScript, PHP and MYSQL.</string>
</resources>
